Andrew Morgan

Email: morganad123@yahoo.com

Career Overview

I am a driven, ambitious, and hardworking young student. In my high school career and throughout my life, I have always been conscientious, dedicated, and committed to doing the best work I could. I have done my very best to achieve good grades as well as to gain what knowledge and pursue opportunities when presented to me. I am a great problem solver although I am not afraid to ask for help when necessary. I have been a part of a few separate video game betas. I have tinkered around with various computer programs and expanded my knowledge of the use of Microsoft Office programs such as Word, PowerPoint, and Excel. I have experience working with Adobe Creative Cloud Programs such as Adobe Animate, Audition, Dreamweaver, Photoshop and Premiere. I also have some familiarity with using Visual Studio, Mono-Develop, Atom, Ionic, and Unity for game and app development on Android, Windows, and IOS platforms. I also have experience using VCV Rack and Chuck to create music for games as well as for implementing musical coding to Unity apps using Chuck's plugin Chunity. I have also done a few projects which involved developing IOS Apps with XCode. I have experience and am familiar with several different languages of code. ActionScript 3, C#, JavaScript, HTML, Python, and Swift are some of the languages that I am familiar with and have written games and apps in.

Qualifications and Technical Skills

Microsoft Office (Word, PowerPoint, Excel)
Adobe Creative Cloud (Adobe Animate, Audition, Dreamweaver, Photoshop, Premiere)
Familiar with ActionScript 3, C#, JavaScript, HTML, Python, and Swift

Job Experience

Job 1: Mowing Lawns for Family Friend

Dates: Summers 2010-2012

Job Title: Lawn Maintenance Specialist

Company or Supervisor: Danielle Cook/Thompson

Duties: Mowing lawns, Weed eating/Line trimming, fertilizing grass

Job 2: Working For The City of Emmett

Dates: 06/04/2014 – 08/29/2014 Job Title: Park/Cemetery Maintenance

Company or Supervisor: Emmett Public Works; Bruce Evans

Address: 316 E Park St, Emmett, ID 83617

Phone: (208) 365-9569

Duties: Mowing Lawns, Push Mowing and or Riding Lawn mowing, Weed eating/Line trimming, planting grass, installing and replacing sprinkler

pipes/systems, road patching/construction

Job 3 Merchandise Flow at Target

Dates: 11/21/2014 - 12/2018

Job Title: Merchandise Flow/Sales Floor

Company or Supervisor: Boise NW Target Store; Harry Gefre, Brian Morris

New Supervisors: Travis, Luis

Address: 6280 N Eagle Rd, Boise, ID 83713

Phone: (208) 938-8350

Duties: Helping to unload trucks, stacking products on pallets, stocking and restocking products onto shelves, setting up cages for cardboard

storage and unloading it into a baler to be smashed, making bales when the baler gets too full.

Job 4 Pack Flow at Amazon

Dates: 1/27/2022 – 8/31/2022 Job Title: Pack Flow/Water Spider

Company or Supervisor: BOI2 Amazon Fulfillment Center; Geoffrey Hurner, Karl Olson

Address: 5319 E Franklin Rd, Nampa, ID 83687, United States

Phone: (208) 466-2647

Duties: Packing, sorting, inducting, picking, tote running, waterspidering. Each of these activities is a step in the process of fulfilling orders for Amazon customers. Placing items into boxes, sorting orders, and scanning items shown on a computer screen were all major parts of the packing and shipping process.

Job 5 Stow at Amazon

Dates: 8/17/2024 - 12/13/2024

Job Title: Stow

Company or Supervisor: BOI2 Amazon Fulfillment Center; Karl Olson Address: 5319 E Franklin Rd, Nampa, ID 83687, United States

Phone: (208) 466-2647

Duties: Scanning, sorting, and stowing items into shelves which carry these items to another location to be processed and sent out to

customers.

Education and Training

School Idaho Inspire Connections Academy

Grad Year 2012 City Emmett State Idaho

Country United States of America

Degree Extra Information High School Diploma I transferred to online schooling from 10th to 12th grade and graduated as Valedictorian of my class. I Maintained and graduated with 3.8 GPA.

GPA: 3.5-3.8

Graduated as Valedictorian

School 2 Boise State University

Grad Year 2021 City Boise State Idaho

Country United States of America

Degree Extra Information I graduated from the Boise State University's College of Innovation and Design with a Bachelor of Science Degree. My major was GIMM or Games Interactive Media and Mobile, which focuses on programming games and apps, as well as learning art and animation styles.

GPA: 3.5